<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>All things adam</title>
    <link>https://bjorkman.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on All things adam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>sv-en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 12:00:11 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bjorkman.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why does people insist on super complicated passwords?</title>
      <link>https://bjorkman.io/blog/showerthoughts1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 12:00:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bjorkman.io/blog/showerthoughts1/</guid>
      <description>So for you guys that does not know, I&amp;rsquo;m currently writting my master thesis on security in smart home assistants (Google Home, Amazon Echo etc.) when a thought struck me; Do users actually care about privacy-?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The cool new toy on the VPN block</title>
      <link>https://bjorkman.io/blog/wireguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bjorkman.io/blog/wireguard/</guid>
      <description>I recently started to fall in love with the new VPN wireguard. For you that does not know, wireguard is a cool new VPN technology that is only around ~4000 lines of code. Not only that; its super fast, overtakingopenVPN protocol bseveral leauges. It is also multicore, which is always nice.
Wireguard uses the ChaCha20 encryption protocol for all its goodiness. I must say however, since the protocol is fairly new, it is not deemd as &amp;ldquo;secure&amp;rdquo; as openVPN or IPSEC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why does people insist on super complicated passwords?</title>
      <link>https://bjorkman.io/blog/passwords/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 12:35:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bjorkman.io/blog/passwords/</guid>
      <description>Something that really grinds my gears is people who still recommends super complex passwords. I mean come on, it&amp;rsquo;s 2018 for christs sake. The old password laws are dead, please just accept that. Just because one pumps a password full with exclamation points, offerings to the devil and half a can of tuna, does not make it a good password. Super complicated passwords such as !#121dsSDA32jKCS(9&amp;rdquo;###!&amp;ldquo;SDd2 are just to much for the simple human mind to handle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://bjorkman.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 13:42:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bjorkman.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Adam. Just your standard swedish asian guy currently attending my last year as a student for M.sc. in Computer Engineering with emphasis on Computer Security at Blekinge Institue of Technology.
Here you will find a good mixture of everything from cryptography to piano, digitalized forever.
Oh. I also do photography.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>