<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on thingsofadam</title>
    <link>https://iNZIGHT.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on thingsofadam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 10:30:30 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://iNZIGHT.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The cool new toy on the VPN block</title>
      <link>https://iNZIGHT.github.io/blog/wireguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 10:30:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iNZIGHT.github.io/blog/wireguard/</guid>
      <description>I recently started to fall in love with the new VPN wireguard. For you that does not know, wireguard is a cool new VPN technology that is only around ~4000 lines of code. Not only that; its super fast, overtakingopenVPN protocol bseveral leauges. It is also multicore, which is always nice.
Wireguard uses the ChaCha20 encryption protocol for all its goodiness. I must say however, since the protocol is fairly new, it is not deemd as &amp;ldquo;secure&amp;rdquo; as openVPN or IPSEC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why does people insist on super complicated passwords?</title>
      <link>https://iNZIGHT.github.io/blog/passwords/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 12:35:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iNZIGHT.github.io/blog/passwords/</guid>
      <description>Something that really grinds my gears is people who still recommends super complex passwords. I mean come on, it&amp;rsquo;s 2018 for christs sake. The old password laws are dead, please just accept that. Just because one pumps a password full with exclamation points, offerings to the devil and half a can of tuna, does not make it a good password. Super complicated passwords such as !#121dsSDA32jKCS(9&amp;quot;###!&amp;ldquo;SDd2 are just to much for the simple human mind to handle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Poem</title>
      <link>https://iNZIGHT.github.io/blog/a-poem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 12:35:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iNZIGHT.github.io/blog/a-poem/</guid>
      <description>Now pleasing sleep had seal&amp;rsquo;d each mortal eye,
Stretch&amp;rsquo;d in the tents the Grecian leaders lie:
The immortals slumber&amp;rsquo;d on their thrones above;
All, but the ever-wakeful eyes of Jove.(76)
To honour Thetis&#39; son he bends his care,
And plunge the Greeks in all the woes of war:
Then bids an empty phantom rise to sight,
And thus commands the vision of the night.
&amp;ldquo;Fly hence, deluding Dream! and light as air,(77)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
